A makeover project
for your most unhinged leftovers.
The best chefs in Korea will
turn your fridge inside out.
The classy cooking show has returned.
-Chef & My Fridge!
-My Fridge!
Hello.
STARTING ANOTHER EPISODE WITH GREAT ENERGY
We're here today
with a webtoon artist and a director
-sitting side by side.
-It's time for the unorthodox clan
-to slowly take over.
-There are too many of them.
-You've now taken up two spots.
-Exactly.
-Let's pull it together.
-I should find another show.
Is anxiety more prevalent
because of this new movement?
One of the chefs
had something they really had to say.
-They wrote us a handwritten letter.
-A handwritten letter?
A HANDWRITTEN LETTER?
-Who was it?
-Let me read the letter we got,
word for word.
"Chef Sung-jun, you recently realized
how popular you were in Hong Kong?"
What is this about?
-Is he asking you to ask that?
-It's for us to ask him.
-It's a question.
-He wrote that himself?
A HANDWRITTEN LETTER
FULL OF DESIRE TO FLAUNT
He asked us to ask this, so I'll do it.
"Chef Sung-jun, you recently realized
how popular you were in Hong Kong?"
FISHING FOR COMPLIMENTS
What was that like?
-I went to Hong Kong last week.
-I see.
And both the show
and I were incredibly popular.
THROWING HIMSELF IN THERE
I held an event there,
and about 200 to 300 people showed up.
I ended up taking
thousands of pictures with them.
-Thousands of photos with 200, 300 people?
-How does it add up?
-They must've taken ten each.
-They wanted ten each.
-We usually count that as one.
-Also,
they asked me to do things like,
"It's an emergency" or "Miss."
THIS?
-Miss.
-They even know what Korean fans don't?
Only I've been doing it.
-Impossible.
-Only we do it to play along.
To humor him.
I guess he looks like
he could be an actor in Hong Kong.
Yes, I think my looks are their type.
-Sammo Hung.
-He's like Sammo Hung.
He has a face
that Hong Kongers don't really like.
-They don't like his face?
-That's right.
-He's not their type.
-What do you know, Amy?
-Is there an overhype?
-Yes.
I believe the overhype is quite serious.
-So what he said was exaggerated.
-It was exaggerated.
There's somebody else
who claimed something similar.
"Chef Jong-won.
I hear you were quite popular in Taiwan."
-This is true.
-It's true.
This one, I can believe it.
-Why is this true?
-Is this also true?
I went to Taiwan
for this very private event,
and hundreds of people showed up,
so I was surprised.
I heard the show
has been airing on their TV,
and our chefs are popular there.
I'M TELLING YOU
I know I shouldn't be like this,
but why does everything he say sound true?
-Right? Let's not be like that.
-That's true.
Is there proof?
You don't have to provide any.
We already have it.
See? These pictures are available.
WHY NOT MY PICTURES?
The picture's out there.
WOW
-Whoa!
-That's a lot.
Look at the second floor.
My crowd was bigger.
I had a bigger crowd.
Where are you, Jong-won?
-Right? Jong-won isn't in the picture.
-He's not.
IS THIS PHOTO REAL?
-You're right!
-He's not in the picture.
JONG-WON'S PHOTO WITHOUT HIM
Some even say
I'm the one who took the photo.
A SELF-TAKEN PHOTO(?)
I knew it.
TAIWANESE FANS,
PLEASE SHOW US PHOTOGRAPHIC PROOF♥
There's another one. "Chef Ho-young.
You went to Taiwan
and finally felt how popular you were."
You don't seem to believe it.
So this was how you all felt?
I've seen it already.
It's on his social media.
He uploaded pictures right away
-on his social media account.
-He did?
-Everyone recognized him.
-He won't hold back.
He won't hold back.
THE ADDICT CAN'T HELP IT
I got lots of likes.
He told me then
that he couldn't even
walk down the street.
-Maybe his legs were hurting.
-Ho-young?
Was the street too narrow?
Was the weather just too hot to walk?
-Well, it was hot.
-Let's see how it was for him.
Let's see if many people showed up.
-That's a lot.
-Impressive.
AMAZED
It looks photoshopped.
-His face looks too slim.
-The shadow looks odd.
-That's not him.
-It's suspicious.
Oh, that's AI-generated.
SUSPICIONS OF AI USAGE
You were cut out from another photo.
Yes, something's odd.
-It's AI-generated.
-It must be.
-It wasn't photoshopped, right?
-No.
SHOW US PROOF, TAIWANESE FANS♥
Now, another chef
decided to turn in
material evidence, not just a photo.
"Chef Hyun-suk.
I heard you visited Singapore."
-Did you bring something?
-What's that?
Did he get us souvenirs?
HANDS SOMETHING OVER
He got these presents.
PRESENTS FROM FANS
Lots of identical plushies.
Are these from a claw machine?
I was told to give it to other chefs.
Their names are on the tags.
AND A NOTE IN KOREAN♥
We'll hand these out to everyone.
And someone asked you
to sign their perfume bottle?
They brought a bottle
labeled "Senior No. 55"
-and asked me to sign it.
-They watched the episode.
-All the details.
-They know everything.
-What's this tiger balm?
-Tiger balm.
It's in the pain plaster form.
How convenient.
Because your shoulders hurt when salting?
They watched everything in detail.
Fan letters used say, "Always be happy"
or "May only good things come your way."
But these days,
it usually says, "Please stay healthy."
It says in Korean,
"Happy birthday, Grandpa!"
When was your birthday?
It's today.
What? Today's your birthday?
IT SEEMS THAT NOBODY KNEW…
I should spend my birthday with my family,
but I'm here shooting this show,
coughing up blood.
If he's coughing up blood,
he shouldn't have come.
I've now truly become Senior No. 55.
You're now 55 years old, legally.
THE BEST AGE IN LIFE, 55
Always stay healthy, and happy birthday.
Now, let's welcome today's guests.
We present
today's fridge owners. Come on out!
Today's fridge owners are
Uhm Jung-hwa and Choi Sooyoung!
Welcome to the show.
-Hello.
-Please come and have a seat.
They're beautiful.
You two just made
the fanciest entrance in our history.
Please allow me to introduce her first.
We've been waiting for her to visit us.
A simply Uhmazing star
with an amazing discography
and filmography,
please welcome Uhm Jung-hwa!
AN UHMAZING GUEST
Hello, everyone.
I'm finally here!
Let's introduce our next guest.
There is a chef
whose wish was to have her on the show.
-There is one.
-Yes, there is.
-Please welcome Sooyoung!
-Sooyoung!
-Hello.
BLUSHING DOUGH GUY
I hear there's a reason
why you two came here together.
-Our film is premiering soon.
-A film.
It's called Okay! Madam 2.
The second in the franchise.
-The second film.
-Yes.
The first film
centered around plane hijacking,
but this time, we're on a cruise.
-A cruise ship?
-Yes, I run into enemies on the ship.
-Me.
-You're her enemy?
-You're the enemy?
-I'm the villain.
IT'S ME, THE VILLAIN
You'll see awesome action scenes
and take a tour
around every corner of the cruise ship.
-It premieres on August 12th.
-August 12th.
-Yes.
-All right.
It already sounds exhilarating,
Okay! Madam 2.
Jung-hwa, did you say you felt like
you came to the show to meet celebrities?
I've been watching the show
since it began.
I love the way
the chefs create these witty dishes,
so I've been dying to meet everyone.
You've singled out a few people
who actually make the show hilarious.
WHICH ONES?
It's Sung-ju and Jung-hwan.
Us?
It's when you go and have a taste.
You go, "Will it fly?"
And he goes, "It won't fly!"
THE HYPER Q&A SESH
Will the dish give more energy?
It's too salty!
It's too sweet!
ON TOP OF THAT…
HE EVEN GETS POSSESSED
DURING THE 5-MINUTE CHECK
You two are hilarious.
She's the first guest
to compliment the hosts.
KUDOS TO THE HOSTS
THEY'RE SO EXCITED…
Sooyoung should've joined us
much earlier than this.
There's someone here who's been
waiting forever for you to come.
Chef Sung-jun.
Back when Yoona was on the show…
While I was an active member of a fansite,
I was nicknamed Sooyoung's Hubby.
-My gosh!
-That's right.
You watched the episode
and even uploaded a post about it.
-I did.
-Yes.
I was really happy to see that.
Stop being so happy.
She's finally here with us.
How do you feel?
First, let me greet her.
I am Kwon Sung-jun, a chef.
What was that?
What's he doing?
-Jeez.
-He's embarrassing me.
IT WAS LIKE
A BOTCHED FIRST LINE AT A BLIND DATE…
THAT WAS THE WORST
My heart is racing too fast today.
He's flushed. Wait, his ears are so red!
-What's with you?
I can't look at her.
Oh, gosh.
Back then, I didn't have many fans
who supported me.
No way.
Taeyeon, Tiffany, and Yoona
were the ones with lots of fans.
I had so few fans
that I'd remember all their usernames.
I'm sure you had a reason
for having her as your bias.
Yes, I've been wanting
to ask you the reason.
Well, I'm someone who has short limbs,
-so I like people with long limbs.
-And hers are long.
Also, she has her own little flair
when she dances.
-What is it?
-She flips her hair.
LIKE THIS
What's that? A hair flair?
I have this thing I do when I dance.
I tend to flip my hair a lot.
-Show us.
-Others do it normally.
-She's up.
-You're so pretty.
But I go…
HAHA…
SUDDENLY FEELS CRINGY
She's suddenly hit with a moment.
-You can do this!
-You got this!
YOU CAN DO IT
Ready, go.
FLIP
STARTING WITH A HAIR FLIP
CASCADING
GREAT JOB
AM I DOING A GREAT JOB?
MOVE ASIDE, EVERYONE
WE HOPE SUNG-JUN CAN BE
LESS HAPPY THAN HE IS NOW…
HER HAIR FLIP CATCHES ATTENTION
You're so beautiful.
Your eyes end up getting drawn to her.
These days, taller members
don't always stand on the side.
Sometimes they even take the center.
-Yes.
-But back then,
taller members usually stood
in the back, off to the side.
Yes, times have changed.
It's better to have
the tallest person stand in the center.
If the tallest one is in the back row,
the perception is lost.
You're right.
To stage a good performance,
it's better for long-limbed members…
Look at her face.
IN TOTAL AGREEMENT
-She should've been in the center.
-Yes.
When you plate your food, I'm sure you put
-the longest piece in the middle.
-Yes.
The center
is always reserved for the longest…
-She knows what's up.
-Yes.
They're a great duo.
THE SHORT-LIMBED GUY IS DISPLEASED…
The tallest person
should be in the middle.
As soon as I saw Girls' Generation,
I felt frustrated.
OH, GOSH…
Why is she back there?
She should be in the front.
-Right?
-Yes.
She should've shown
the impact of her hair flip
in the very front
to let it flare out to the edges.
When will he be done?
I'll… What were you doing?
Why didn't you protest?
I'm sorry.
You probably weren't a huge fan.
-You should've…
-He faked it.
Fans often protest with trucks these days.
You should've sent one yourself.
You should've demanded
that I stand in the center.
SPEECHLESS…
If Sooyoung was in the center,
the impact of K-pop
in the world's history would've shifted.
It would've changed.
-She would've gone first.
-I would've.
-I would've gone to Coachella.
-You would have!
INTIMIDATED…
Next year is our 20th anniversary,
-so show me some support.
-Of course.
I'll drive my car there and protest.
A MODEST 1-PERSON PROTEST…
I should've debuted again now.
So you are.
Yes, I am.
I'M DEBUTING SOON
-Girls' Generation-HRS.
-Yes.
SHE'LL DEBUT AS A UNIT,
GIRLS' GENERATION-HRS
Back when Hyo-yeon visited us,
you were yet to start
your official promotion.
Yes, but we gained lots of popularity,
so we ended up making our actual debut.
Why couldn't they change the name?
Girls' Generation-SHR.
-SHR? Or SRH.
-Girls' Generation-SRH.
S for Sooyoung
should be in the very front.
-I'm sorry.
-But it's…
That was a bit of a stretch.
That's a good one.
That unit is already doing so well.
I demanded that I be the center
for Girls' Generation-HRS,
but Hyo-yeon said…
You're like the middle finger.
Right. Like the Chinese character
for mountain.
COME TO THINK OF IT, MAYBE…
Like the character for mountain.
I've been getting pulled
in all directions.
SAD FOR HER
What's this song that gave you energy
whenever you were down?
A song that gave you energy?
-It's called "Rule of the Princess."
-"Rule of the Princess"?
-I've never heard of it.
Not "Princess Is Lonely"?
-"Princess Is Lonely."
-"Rule of the Princess"?
It's about that strong princess spirit.
That's nice.
-I see.
-That's nice.
Doesn't it make you emotional?
-It does.
-It makes me feel like crying.
She's connecting with the song.
She seemed impressed by the lyrics.
This makes you emotional?
Are you a type T?
CAN'T RELATE…
-"Don't chase the stars. Be a star."
-Live as a star.
Our chefs have been stressed out
with the heightened competition.
-It's tough.
-Sam?
Did you just hear the lyrics?
A TENACIOUS STAR-OBSESSED CHEF
Fetch Me the Star, Lamb.
Don't chase the stars, be a star yourself.
That was moving.
HE WASN'T EVEN PAYING ATTENTION…
Sung-jun, what do you do to stay calm?
Of course. When times are tough,
I listen to a song
called "Lion Heart."
Everything he says sounds like a lie.
-I'm serious.
-It just sounds like a lie.
Can you sing a phrase
to help you stay strong?
It's a bit too high.
His credibility just dropped.
-What? Why?
-Right? Isn't that so?
-You felt it, right?
-Yes.
He did it like it was scripted.
-Why?
-She's now suspicious of Sung-jun.
So Sooyoung gets lots of energy
from the song "Rule of the Princess."
Now, I wonder what she has in her fridge.
We're getting curious.
Do you use it alone?
-Yes.
-I see.
It's been about seven years
-that I've lived alone.
-Seven years?
Let's find out what she has.
-We present Sooyoung's fridge!
-Fridge!
WOOHOO
She doesn't have a lot.
-Emergency.
-It's a bit…
Quite a lot of empty space.
She's been busy filming.
Because I live alone,
I often find myself throwing food out
after it expires.
-It happens when living alone.
-It's not easy.
The top shelf has side dishes.
There are lots of basic side dishes.
They might be spoiled.
-It's been there for a while.
-Is that so?
SNIFF
-This one is a goner.
-It's been a while.
OH BOY
-Wait a second.
-It smells sour.
-Really?
-Is that kimchi?
-It's meat, but it's…
-The meat smells sour?
The meat smells sour.
-Oh, it's expired.
-Right?
It smells that sour?
I thought it was mukeunji.
It's delicious after a toss in a pan.
We should throw it out.
No, please don't.
I'll check and eat it if I can.
WHAT?
It'll be fine once it's warm.
No, you can't do that.
IT'S NOT OKAY…
She's different.
But it's not moldy.
-No way.
-It could be moldy somewhere.
-I'll eat it instead.
-By the time it smells sour…
I'll eat it.
-Hey.
-Sung-jun, what?
-You can't.
-I'll eat it for lunch.
You can't.
-I'll leave it out here.
-No way.
THIS IS FOR SUNG-JUN
-It looks good.
-I'm worried about the next one.
What's this?
-Bean sprouts.
AUTOMATICALLY SMELLS IT FIRST…
It's a little unwell.
It's unwell.
It hasn't gone completely bad yet.
Can you smell things fine?
Do you have a sinus infection?
I think I lost my sense of smell
after the COVID-19 pandemic.
IN HER PRINCESS SPIRIT,
SHE'LL PLAY ALONG WITH EVERYTHING♥
Here's a tip from the production crew.
Sooyoung had once gone
to the emergency room while eating.
-After eating that?
-Did your stomach hurt?
Once I get a taste of something delicious,
I continue to eat and eat.
I like
those cold kimchi noodles they have
at barbecue places for wrap parties.
The kind that's served on the side.
I was eating that,
and then I suddenly had a headache.
It felt like I had food up to my neck
and had cut off circulation to my head.
-You ate that much?
-Was it indigestion?
So I got my stomach pumped
at the emergency room.
You just force yourself to keep eating?
I'm more captivated by the flavor
-than the fullness.
-I know that.
-I know what she means.
-Because it's that good?
Nam-no, can you understand this situation?
Have you had indigestion?
I suffer from it often.
You often suffer from it?
I've been to the emergency room too.
-What?
-For eating too much?
I was in my mid-twenties,
and I had tried top-grade Korean beef
for the first time.
It was so good that it made my head spin.
-Made his head spin?
-I alone probably had
about 1.1 kg of beef
along with somaek, soju and beer.
-My head is spinning now.
-Over a kilogram?
-About eight portions then.
-It was my first time.
When you're too full,
oxygen level drops in your head.
-He's right.
-Oxygen?
They had the same symptoms,
but they ended up in two different shapes.
THE MYSTERIES OF THE HUMAN BODY
So you enjoy eating?
I love to eat. I love delicious things.
I see cheese on the next shelf.
-She has lots of cheese.
-There's burrata.
You must like cheese.
I like to grind…
-And sprinkle it?
-…and sprinkle it on pasta as a kick.
I see. Used as a kick.
Are these anchovies?
-They are.
-Anchovies, right?
I love anchovy pasta.
-That sounds good.
-I wanted to get it,
so I bought one
during my visit to America,
but I haven't used it yet.
-There they are.
-She has them.
-You have pasta too.
-Yes.
-She has pasta.
-Do you make it?
-Yes, at times.
-I'll make anchovy pasta.
-When I crave pasta…
-That's mine.
…but don't want to get it delivered,
I make pasta for myself.
So she does cook at home.
I try to maximize…
I mean, minimize the number of tools I use
whenever I cook.
Cleaning up is a hassle.
It's such a hassle.
I should cook for her.
You're the type that can't be bothered.
Yes, I'm like that.
I even wonder
if using the cutting board is necessary.
I sit and wonder…
-Scissors?
-…if I should use it.
I'd end up resorting to scissors,
and if my half-hearted attempt works,
I tell myself,
"I'm glad I didn't use the board."
Or you can get pre-prepped vegetables.
-But I don't like to use those.
-Not those?
I believe you must cut the ingredients
on the spot as you cook.
-I can connect.
-Right?
Right? The pre-cut ones…
-Those are lifeless.
-Yes, they're lifeless.
They're lifeless?
"INGREDIENTS MUST HAVE LIFE"
BY MS. CHOI
Is your food good?
I think I make
pretty good stuff.
She's confident.
We need an objective answer.
I never even have to check while cooking.
I have a good sense
of figuring out when it's perfect.
-I believe cooking is all about timing.
-Timing.
Those who fail at cooking
probably fail because of their impatience.
Keep staring
and lock into a power struggle
with your food.
"Not yet."
And then! I finish it.
-Right.
-The timing.
I'm also an expert at making porridge.
-Porridge?
Porridge.
After we're done with shabu-shabu,
we always finish the meal
-with porridge, right?
-Yes, you're right.
-That's porridge.
-When I eat shabu-shabu with my staff,
I'm always in charge
of making the porridge,
and it's to die for.
PORRIDGE PRIDE
-It sounds good.
-Waiting is key when making porridge.
The timing for adding the egg
is very important.
-It's important.
-That moment
when you mix the egg in.
-Then work with the residual heat.
-Exactly!
-You know exactly what's up.
-Yes.
-As it simmers.
-Lastly, a drop of sesame oil.
At the very end.
Too early, and you lose the aroma.
We won't allow that.
-Right at the end.
-You know what's up.
You just can't be bothered,
-but when you actually do it…
-I do it right.
What's this?
-Freshwater snails.
-Freshwater snails?
-Salmon.
-Salmon?
-Duck.
-Jamón.
-Right.
I consider protein very important,
so even when I don't want to cook,
I still want to have some protein.
When I have time, I'd make
a huge batch of freshwater snail doenjang
and eat veggie and rice wraps
with that as the sauce.
I eat salmon and jamón
to make American-style breakfast,
served with some bread and eggs.
This is sweet jelly,
and there's a princess right here.
-Gongju, just like "gongju" for princess.
-Yes.
-Red bean jelly with chestnuts. Yanggaeng.
-"Rule of the Princess."
I see some alcohol on this side.
I see your name on this bottle.
One of my fans engraved it with my name
-and gave it to me…
-A rosé?
-…for my birthday.
-That's a thing?
-February 10th, 1990. Is that right?
-You're right.
That's when you got it?
-No.
-No, that's just my birthday.
-It's her birthday.
-Her birthday.
-Can you drink a bottle alone?
-Yes.
-I can do that.
-A bottle of wine.
How much alcohol can you take, Jung-hwa?
I'm just like her.
She can take much more alcohol than I can.
-We're about the same.
-Excuse me.
Are you talking about the magnum size?
A BOTTLE OF THIS?
-Just a regular bottle.
-One.
A bottle of wine,
a bottle of whiskey, and a bottle of soju.
-A bottle of different kinds?
-One bottle each.
What's Jung-hwa like
after she drinks a little?
She can be really adorable.
-I begin to laugh a lot.
-Yes, she does that.
Sooyoung dances.
-You do?
-Yes.
Do you do the flips?
This hair thing. The flip.
I wanted to be cute when I was with her.
A CUTE JUNIOR ACTOR♥
What's in here?
-Bread.
-Is that focaccia?
-That is
my favorite, called slab bread.
That's huge.
It's big enough to be used as a cushion.
Or a pillow.
I also love figs,
so I like to eat them
with pistachio spread,
-by turning them into a sandwich.
-So you make a sandwich.
-Chicken.
-You have some chicken here.
I really like spicy braised chicken.
That's not an easy dish to make.
I can even make it with my feet.
DROP THE MIC
I see. She dribbles the ingredients.
Now, non-perishable ingredients.
Oh, you must drink tea at home.
I was deeply into tea ceremonies
for a while.
She was into tea ceremonies?
But after just two times, I just…
-Couldn't be bothered?
-…couldn't be bothered.
HER CHRONIC LAZINESS KICKED IN
-I couldn't do it.
-You end up using a mug.
-You have to throw out the dregs.
-I get it.
I picked it up
because the time I waited
for the tea to brew made me…
-It's calming.
-Yes, it was quite calming.
Then one day,
I realized I could be more patient
even without brewing the tea.
I began to wonder
if this action was necessary
for me to build more patience,
so I did some self-reflection,
and switched all my teas to tea bags.
CONVENIENCE IS THE BEST
-It's convenient.
-That's true.
Tea bags are delicious.
That's it for Sooyoung's fridge!
I wonder what her orders might be.
Let's find out what they are.
Show us.
-First order. Rule of the Princess's Dish.
-Rule of the Princess's Dish.
LIKE THE SONG SHE MENTIONED
Make her a princess?
I've recently been
too busy to eat right.
All I eat is simples things
like salad or gimbap,
so I've been craving
something very fancy and grand.
I GET IT
So I want something very fancy
that can recharge my energy
as a princess.
-A fancy dish.
-Like a big treat.
But the thing is, my ingredients
are a bit too humble.
Our chef will
dress them up like a princess.
-Yes, of course.
-She needs that princess energy.
Here's the second order.
Don't Skip Meals
Because You Can't Be Bothered.
You seemed to be quite lazy.
I often can't be bothered,
so I want to eat something
that's easy and breezy to make
but also very delicious.
That's what I want.
Now, take a look at the orders
and jump in, chefs.
There is someone
who had been dying to have her here,
-Sooyoung's Hubby.
-We should have him choose first.
I'm going to pick something, but…
GETS UP
What's that?
The princess seemed chilly.
Wait, what the heck?
A BLANKET FOR PRINCESS SOOYOUNG
-Yes, it's a bit chilly.
-Isn't it cold?
THE PRINCESS WHO FEELS COLD
AND A MAN WHO NOTICED
I was keeping an eye on her,
and she seemed cold.
MOVED
WHAT DID I JUST WITNESS?
When I said I was cold, you just said…
-You did?
-…"Why are you cold?"
Dang it.
Jung-hwa also seems a bit chilly.
LOL
Please don't.
-Look at her. She's also cold.
-Sit down.
-No?
-She's fine.
-What are you doing?
-She seemed chilly.
This won't be enough.
-Sung-jun, you get the first pick.
-Yes, I should go first.
Of course, I'll go
-with Rule of the Princess's Dish.
-Rule of the Princess's Dish.
I've been waiting for this day.
Then who's going to challenge
Sung-jun, aka Sooyoung's Hubby?
GLANCES
RAISING HAND
WHAT?
This princess deserved to stand
in the center a long time ago.
I'll give her what she deserves.
HYUN-SUK PICKS RULE OF THE PRINCESS'S DISH
He can be Sooyoung's Unc,
like an older guy fan.
Hyun-suk joins the first round.
That's interesting.
Don't Skip Meals
Because You Can't Be Bothered.
-I'll join.
-Hey.
-Nam-no?
-Yes, the can't-be-bothered round.
But he can always be bothered for food.
I'm going to use
a minimal amount of cooking
to maximize the flavors.
-He's good at that.
-He is.
You actually understood the order.
Yes, I actually managed
to figure it out today.
Something you can do with your feet.
Do it with your feet.
I've never cooked with my feet.
SHE DOESN'T MEAN IT LITERALLY…
Who wants to face Nam-no?
Or join it for the order.
I'll go.
EUN-YEONG PICKS DON'T SKIP MEALS
BECAUSE YOU CAN'T BE BOTHERED
I also have that lazy side,
You do.
…and it's been a while
since I've won a star.
So I want to take down Chef Nam-no,
our weakest contestant,
-and change the course.
-"Weakest"?
That was harsh.
How did he end up becoming the weakest?
That's Nam-no versus Eun-yeong then.
Let us begin Rule of the Princess's Dish,
a round between Hyun-suk and Sung-jun!
I've got chills. I'm excited.
This is great.
-I'm so excited.
-All right.
This is the first cook-off
with Sooyoung's ingredients.
Sooyoung's Hubby for 20 years,
Chef Kwon Sung-jun,
versus the guy
who's willing to be her grandpa,
Chef Choi Hyun-suk.
They played as a team
in the previous episode.
After that team round,
Hyun-suk said he aged by a decade
after cooking with Sung-jun.
-Did you say this?
-Why?
It's much easier
to have Sung-jun as my opponent
than to work with him in a team.
IT MUST'VE BEEN QUITE A JOURNEY…
For a team round,
we're supposed to work together
and make the dishes together.
But when we were discussing recipes,
he wasn't looking for teamwork.
He said, "You're going to do that?
I'll do this then."
EACH ON THEIR OWN
He refuses to mix.
I don't always have to be
the one to score the goal.
I just want the team to win.
But this guy needs to score
the most decisive goal himself.
It has to go through him.
What's your take on this account?
I completely agree.
-You do?
-Yes.
This cook-off today
-must have a special meaning for you.
-It does.
The one you've always waited for,
-Sooyoung, is finally here.
-"Sooyoung's Hubby."
-I didn't want to bring up this data, but…
-What is it?
He's jinxed at the moment.
-Don't bring it up.
-I know.
Everyone and their mother knows this.
Every time a K-pop idol star
brings their fridge to the studio…
He lost all ten rounds.
He hasn't won once.
-He's jinxed.
-How does this happen?
-It's that bad?
-Here's the thing.
Before receiving a star
from the first bias of my life, Sooyoung,
I couldn't take it from anyone else.
SUSPICIOUS
But you tried hard to win.
To a man, his first love will always be
unforgettable.
SHRIEK!
Is there a cockroach?
-I'll throw these at him. I will.
-What happened?
You're really desperate.
Her star has a whole new meaning.
CHEF HYUN-SUK'S INGREDIENTS:
GRAVLAX, SLICED CHEESE, BURRATA
YUJA PEPPER PASTE, ZUCCHINI, SHRIMP,
CURRY POWDER, CHAMPAGNE, AND MORE
First up, Chef Hyun-suk.
What are you making?
The name of my dish is Choipunzel.
-Choipunzel.
-Choipunzel?
Rapunzel is my favorite princess.
SOOYOUNG'S BIAS, RAPUNZEL
-Emergency.
-You did it again, Hyun-suk.
You express your beauty and charm
using your hair, right?
There's a thin kind of pasta in Italy
called angel hair.
So I'll make pasta today
with princess hair,
along with a pretty appetizer
for the princess's meal.
-My gosh. I'm so excited.
-European royalty
would travel around with private chefs
and use different ingredients
as they moved to different countries.
I'll be your private chef,
follow you around the world,
and make your food with local ingredients.
LEAVE IT TO ME, PRINCESS
VERY PLEASED♥
-How cool.
-Not angel hair.
Are you going to make
this princess hair yourself?
-I'll do it myself.
-Fresh pasta?
Because store-bought pasta
cannot embody Sooyoung's beautiful hair.
So you're making fresh pasta?
Can he make thin noodles?
-Angel hair is really thin.
-It has to be very thin.
I'm not sure if it'll be possible.
CHEF SUNG-JUN'S INGREDIENTS:
ANCHOVY, CAPER, GRAVLAX, JAMÓN
YANGGAENG WITH CHESTNUTS, SEAWEED BUGAK,
PISTACHIO CREAM, BURRATA, AND MORE
Sung-jun must feel anxious.
So what are you making?
The dish I prepared is…
It's called Into Three New Worlds.
Into the New World?
DOESN'T WANT TO MEET THE NEW SUNG-JUN
It's a parody of "Into the New World,"
so it's Into Three New Worlds.
-Three.
-I prepared
a three-course Italian meal.
You're making three dishes?
I've never made
actual authentic pasta here.
I thought it'd be expected of me.
But even though it's a cliché,
I want to face Hyun-suk head-on
by making a very delicious dish.
-Gosh, I'm so excited.
-The first one is the appetizer.
Pistachio, burrata, and ham
create a great balance.
I'll make them into the shape of a flower.
Next, I'm going to make anchovy pasta.
-She said she liked it.
-You mentioned it earlier.
I'm making anchovy oil pasta,
and topping it with gravlax tartar
to make it even fancier.
And lastly,
I'll use chestnut yanggaeng from Gongju
for the princess, gongju,
-and make panna cotta.
-Panna cotta.
-In 15 minutes?
THREE DISHES FOR PRINCESS SOOYOUNG
You have a favor to ask her
if you end up winning today?
Since my first year
at Eulji Middle School,
I've always dreamed of this one moment.
"Into the New World" with her.
-Does he want to dance?
-With her?
I want to dance with her.
If you put yourself in her shoes,
she may not want to do it.
She might end up
not choosing you intentionally.
-I've dreamed of this for 20 years.
-His dream of 20 years.
If he wins, he wants to dance with you.
I decline.
We also don't want to see it.
-You'll have to agree first.
-Yes.
Getting declined
wasn't a part of my dream.
-For now, let's try to win.
-First, I'll win.
-You'll have to win first.
-She might agree to dance with you.
You just have to win.
She's trying to make this fair
for Chef Hyun-suk.
And now, let us begin the round.
-I'm so excited.
-Excellent.
He has waited 20 years for this day.
Sooyoung's Hubby of Eulji Middle School,
Chef Kwon Sung-jun.
FLATTERED AND EMBARRASSED
He claims Sooyoung
is the center of Girls' Generation
and he's the center of Chef & My Fridge.
Here to show the class as the center,
Chef Hyun-suk is up against him.
Which one will become
Princess Sooyoung's private chef?
Let the 15-minute cook-off begin!
A DISH FOR THE PRINCESS
-He starts with pasta.
-Yes.
-Sung-jun uses regular pasta.
Please make her a very fancy meal.
He said he'd make panna cotta,
so I'm curious to see how he'll do that.
He needs something similar to cream.
-There are no ingredients like that.
-She didn't have gelatin, either.
No, she didn't have gelatin.
It won't be easy to make in time.
Is he just too ambitious?
That's vanilla syrup.
He threw the sweet jelly into milk,
and then some vanilla syrup.
She doesn't have gelatin,
but this comes with agar.
That sweet jelly includes agar,
so it can harden.
That was smart.
However, it does take forever!
It's been a minute already.
-Whoa.
-What's Hyun-suk using? Salmon?
Yes, that's gravlax.
-So it's salmon.
-It's not smoked salmon.
-He's matching the sizes.
-Salmon and cheese?
Yes, it's cheese.
He's stacking layers of salmon and cheese.
He must be trying to make a shape.
D'OH…
NEXT, SALMON!
Your hands have been
trembling a lot more lately.
He can't help it.
His hands have become shakier.
They're shaking more violently.
Put a pain plaster on.
-He's putting burrata in the middle.
-That's burrata?
I guess he'll use lots of that.
What's that?
It's called yuzu kosho,
a sauce made with yuja and pepper.
-I really like that paste.
-It's made with everything you like.
I can't wait to find out what it's like.
Sung-jun is also using salmon.
Sung-jun's using salmon.
I am.
But he's…
CHOPPING!
It's like makhoe, sliced raw fish.
-It's tartar.
-Tartar.
-Salmon tartar.
Lemon zest.
LEMON JUICE
OLIVE OIL
Is that for the anchovy pasta?
It's the topping.
I see.
It's hard to imagine what it's like.
She really loves salmon.
It's been two minutes,
and apparently Sooyoung loves salmon.
RED PEPPER
Yes, she likes anchovies and salmon.
3. COOK ANCHOVIES, GARLIC,
RED PEPPER, AND CAPERS IN OLIVE OIL
CUT THE SLAB BREAD INTO A ROUND SHAPE
4. COAT THE CIRCULAR BREAD
WITH ANCHOVY OIL AND TOAST
TOASTING IN THE OVEN
SALMON CHEESE ROLL
TURNING 90 DEGREES
I think Hyun-suk wants to roll that,
but it doesn't seem to work.
It is working.
I just got the direction confused.
You're at that age.
FUMING
PLEASE STAY HEALTHY…
How pretty.
It looks like a lobster.
COOKING FOIL
-Huh?
-If he's covering it in foil,
it means he'll cook it somehow.
-In the oven?
-Will you grill it?
-But the cheese will melt.
-He'll cool it down.
It's just for the shape.
-Just the shape?
He's just keeping it in shape
and letting it sit.
Sung-jun makes panna cotta.
What's important for panna cotta…
-…is for it to solidify.
-Right.
Because agar doesn't turn solid quickly.
-It takes time.
-It takes a while.
It has to be at a certain temperature.
POURING INTO GLASSES
-So he'll harden them like that?
-But will they?
People are worried over here.
MR. CHESTNUT TIRAMISU'S
CHESTNUT YANGGAENG PANNA COTTA!
HYUN-SUK BEGINS MAKING PASTA DOUGH
I need some salt.
SALT
THIS ISN'T IT!
LET'S ADD THE FLAIR!
I know. That's the flair.
-The hair flip.
-The hair?
SOOYOUNG IS HER GROUP'S CENTER!
I'M THE SHOW'S CENTER!
He'll complain about neck pain next week.
-He's making the pasta dough.
-The pasta dough.
That looks great.
-I hope it turns out nicely.
-It seems so.
-Princess hair. It has to be thin.
-It looks great.
HOW DO YOU POWDER THE DOUGH?
LIKE THIS!
HEARTTHROB
That's the princess's hair flip.
It's his flair show.
WATCH ME!
STAYING TRUE TO THE CONCEPT
HE'S ALL ABOUT PERFORMING
LIKE A FOOL
THE HAIR FLIP DOES GRAB
EVERYONE'S ATTENTION
He's like a dark wizard.
I wonder what
his princess hair pasta will look like.
-It's his own pasta.
-It'd better be thin.
That's the dough.
You can almost see through it.
IT'S EXHILARATING!
IT ALWAYS FEELS NEW!
His face is slowly becoming white.
He keeps sprinkling flour on himself.
A FUN FLAIR, WASN'T IT?
And 9 minutes left,
9 minutes and 30 seconds.
It's been nine minutes already.
SOOYOUNG'S HUBBY IS VERY SERIOUS TODAY
Zucchini.
ADDING ZUCCHINI TO THE ANCHOVY BASE
What are you cooking, Sung-jun?
The pasta base.
Sung-jun is using
ordinary store-bought pasta.
IN!
It looks good. It already looks great.
He's really good with dried noodles.
Wait, you're adding plain water?
Why plain water?
-In case it's too salty.
-Too salty?
-I think that's why.
-Is that the recipe?
-It's not.
-It's an anchovy pasta,
-so I have to taste it.
-It's his thing.
It's such a wonder that
they can cook while listening to everyone.
-That's the toughest part.
-Isn't it?
-But it's a must.
-It must be tough to focus.
-It is.
-Exactly.
-But we do it.
-You're the most… The loudest.
That's my role.
-There's no time.
-He keeps talking to them.
What's that?
White balsamic vinegar.
White balsamic? Blast it!
WHAT?
POONG IS TRYING SO HARD
SO THAT'S HIS ROLE!
Eight and a half minutes.
It's better to finish first
since you're both making noodles.
-It's more advantageous.
-You'd better finish first.
SHRIMP, GARLIC
What's that?
-Pine nuts?
-Garlic.
Pistachio cream.
What's that? Pistachio?
What are you making, Sung-jun?
Pistachio pesto.
-Pistachio pesto.
-Right. Whoa.
7. MIX PISTACHIO CREAM, OLIVE OIL, SALT,
GROUND PEPPER, GRANA PADANO, PECORINO
-Eight minutes left.
-Eight minutes.
ZUCCHINI
STARTING ON THE PASTA SAUCE!
7. COOK SHRIMP,
CRUSHED GARLIC, AND ZUCCHINI
AND CHAMPAGNE!
He cooked the shrimps.
Champagne.
BLAST?
THE 1ST ROW GETS WET
SPINNING AROUND
WHOA…
THE 2ND ROW ALSO GETS WET
STARTING WITH A CHAMPAGNE POP!
What have you done, Hyun-suk?
C… CONGRATS
What was that just now?
-Chef Hyun-suk!
-Waterbomb Festival.
This is what I call
the Waterbomb Festival!
EVERYONE HAS FUN, THANKS TO THE GRANDPA
WE WISH TO CELEBRATE
YOUR NEXT BIRTHDAY TOGETHER TOO
I think he got some in his pan.
What is this?
LOL
He looks flustered.
EVERYONE'S HAPPY DAY
What is this?
I didn't know it would explode. I'm sorry.
-Did it go into Sung-jun's pan?
-Into every single one.
It got into everything.
Hyun-suk looks flustered.
THAT'S HYUN-SUK'S ROLE
-I didn't know it'd explode. I'm sorry.
-That's insane.
Six and a half minutes.
8. ADD WHITE SOY SAUCE, CURRY POWDER,
AND OLIVE OIL INTO THE SAUCE
-He's the king of performing.
-I think he's celebrating his birthday.
He's saying his food is good.
That was hilarious.
Six minutes left.
Wait, what happened here?
Weren't you going to make flowers?
I will.
-He grabs jamón.
-So he'll make flowers with those.
Oh, he's making flowers with jamón?
He's making a flower using jamón.
-A flower.
-It's like a rose.
-It looks nice.
-How pretty.
HOW ABOUT WHAT'S IN THE OVEN?
-What's that?
-It's bread.
-It's toasted bread.
-You're already plating the dish?
-He's quick.
-That is so cool.
-He's so cool.
-He is?
Yes.
The angel hair.
-It's done.
-The princess hair!
-It should be thin.
-Is it ready?
That's thicker than I thought.
I have thick hair,
-so it's just like mine.
-She says that the thickness is fine.
It looks great.
FLAIR!
THE KING OF FLAIR
He continues doing that
even after the champagne incident.
The princess hair pasta looks good.
And he cooks it right away.
They have less than five minutes left.
Sung-ju, only five minutes remain.
Please go check the dishes.
I'll report from the kitchen.
That pasta looks so good.
His pasta is no joke. Mantecare!
My gosh.
He has to do what he's good at.
My gosh. That is so cool.
You're so cool.
Hyun-suk is doing a lot too.
He's using two burners.
-Wait.
-Try this one?
WHOA
How dare he point like that?
KEEPING THE YOUNG GUNS IN LINE
Let me try the pasta sauce.
This is my favorite part.
I'll try this pasta sauce.
-The pasta sauce.
-Will he get a star from a K-pop star?
WILL THIS END HIS 10 CONSECUTIVE LOSSES?
Again, it's not so promising.
DELIGHTED TO WATCH HER FAVORITE PART LIVE
WHY?
It lacks umami.
-No umami?
-It's a bit bland.
-There's ramyeon soup base!
-It's bland.
Use the ramyeon soup base!
-It's right there!
-Ramyeon soup base for pasta?
You can do this, Hubby.
"You can do this, Hubby"?
She said, "You can do this, Hubby!"
CALM YET FAZED
-It's okay.
-It's bland.
Can you also go, "Keep it up, Grandpa"?
Keep it up, Unc!
THE "GOTCHA" FLAIR
STAYING TRUE TO HIS ROLE
Chef Hyun-suk is doing a lot too.
This cheese and salmon thing is ready.
10. ASSEMBLE, POUR THE SAUCE
It looks good.
It already looks delicious.
ADDING THE PRINCESS HAIR PASTA!
That looks really good.
-This one.
-That looks great too.
What's that?
-What is this?
-Curry powder.
-He added curry powder.
SUNG-JUN BEGINS TO PLATE HIS FOOD TOO
BURRATA
He's calm.
9. TOP SLAB BREAD WITH BURRATA,
PISTACHIO PESTO, JAMÓN, ARUGULA
Hyun-suk looks up at the time
while doing his best!
Yes!
And he doesn't forget the hair flip!
HIS PERFORMANCE NEVER ENDS
He did mantecare with his curry pasta!
You got this, Unc!
Three minutes and twenty seconds.
Does it take this little time
to make fresh pasta?
I know, it came out really fast.
Blonde hair.
-It's the princess's blonde hair.
-The blonde hair.
-That's why he added curry.
-That's why.
-The blonde hair.
-It smells so good.
Three minutes!
Let me check Hyun-suk's pasta.
The princess hair.
Does the princess hair pasta
flutter in your mouth?
HER FAVORITE PART
DELICIOUS WITH A FLAIR!
CHOI HYUN-SUK FINISHES CHOIPUNZEL
Two minutes and forty seconds.
Look.
WITH 2 MINUTES AND 40 SECONDS TO SPARE!
He had 2 minutes and 40 seconds left.
-He did that in 13 minutes?
-It only took 13 minutes.
It's the blonde princess's hair.
The blonde hair.
SUNG-JUN MUST MAKE THREE COURSES
FIRST, PRESENT THE PASTA NICELY
SEAWEED BUGAK
You have time.
Sung-jun puts in
everything he has toward the end.
Will he break his jinx with K-pop stars?
Will he break it?
Will he save his reputation
-as Sooyoung's fan?
-Lemon zest.
-You can relax.
-You have time.
ARUGULA
He's not joking around today.
The pasta is ready.
He just needs to finish the panna cotta.
One minute left!
I hope it hardened.
I think he's conscious of the fact
that Sooyoung is only looking at him.
He's keeping a straight face.
"I am not superficial."
NOW'S THE TIME!
Are you still waiting?
-"Into the New World."
-As I dance.
TO PANNA COTTA AS HE DANCES!
He looks at the time.
He's looking at the time and waiting.
Why is he trying so hard to look cool?
Why does he stand like this?
Sung-jun waits for Sooyoung.
"Why isn't she showing up?"
-Where is she? Twenty seconds.
-I'm curious.
He finally pulls them out.
Panna cotta.
IT HARDENED!
-It hardened.
-Quickly.
-Panna cotta.
The panna cotta hardened.
So he decided to freeze it. And it worked.
Two seconds. Wrap it up! Time's up.
That's the time.
Sung-jun finishes his dishes too.
Gosh. That was such a wonder.
It's so cool to watch it in person.
-It is.
-They're so cool.
Both meals are ready for Sooyoung.
THE PRINCESS SHALL BEGIN HER FEAST
These will turn you into a princess.
AMAZED
My gosh. Really?
Both meals are ready for Sooyoung.
She wanted something really fancy
suitable for a princess.
Do you like it?
Just looking at these
already makes me so happy.
All right.
First, please try
Chef Hyun-suk's dish first, Choipunzel.
A SALMON CHEESE ROLL FOR THE PRINCESS
FRESH SHRIMP CURRY PASTA
REPRESENTING RAPUNZEL'S HAIR
CHEF CHOI HYUN-SUK'S CHOIPUNZEL
-It's a salmon and cheese roll.
-It is.
-And a piece of bread.
-Gosh. I'm so excited.
Sooyoung looks really excited.
It's easy to cut.
-You look like a princess right now.
-Right?
Yes, even the dish
is something a princess would use.
ASTONISHED
-Like the royalty.
-The royalty.
-What does it smell like?
-Yum.
THE PRINCESS TAKES HER FIRST BITE
"Yum"?
That looks so good.
-Cheese, salmon, and bread.
-It might be too salty.
LAUGHING
It must be good.
She suddenly burst out laughing.
The princess looks pleased.
How did he make this?
COMPLETELY AMAZED
It's an emergency.
What's in the roll?
-Burrata.
As well as the yuja pepper paste she had
to balance out
the saltiness and the richness.
I became a bit suspicious
when he added the yuja pepper paste.
-She said it could be too salty.
-Right.
It does taste salty,
but this sweetness balances it out.
She had white balsamic vinegar,
which can be too sweet.
So I added some lemon juice
for sourness to make it more appetizing.
I want another bite.
-Have more.
-Go ahead.
These are all your ingredients.
-I'm so happy.
-You can have it all.
How did he make this with my ingredients?
So this is the fun of Chef & My Fridge.
If you can be bothered a little,
-you can make that yourself.
-Of course.
He made that
with everything you had in your fridge.
-He's turning her into a princess.
-Gosh, it's so good.
-Next, the pasta.
-It looks good.
It already tasted perfect
when he had three minutes left.
He had to flip his hair and everything
to make that pasta.
Will it please her appetite?
The princess's…
-Huh?
-Oh, no.
ROLLING OFF
That's mine.
-This?
-Yours?
It's hers.
-That's yours?
-I'll taste it.
-I picked it up for you.
-Has it been three seconds?
SLURP
I wonder what the pasta is like.
MMM
It looks good.
Chef Hyun-suk cranes his neck,
waiting for your response.
It has a Japanese twist to it.
A JAPANESE TWIST?
It's like
a really old restaurant you run into
in rural Japan,
a place that's really good.
-Made by a country grandpa.
-Yes.
So I found this place,
creaked open the old door,
and the place only has
one thing on the menu.
An old country man?
An old expert.
So I ordered curry pasta, and…
Delicious.
Delish-love you.
Did you mean to add the Japanese twist?
The princess is traveling
with her private chef
to Japan.
-I love the storyline.
-I knew it.
Does that mean
I should consider this dish
a trip to Italy?
-Where's this? Italy.
-Italy.
It's like I'm on a cruise ship
going between Italy and Japan.
-You should've said that.
-That's it.
A cruise ship that set sail in Italy
and will arrive in Japan.
THAT'S AN INSANE INTERPRETATION
I think this dish
has been meticulously planned out.
Topping salmon on top of grain bread
is done in North Europe,
in countries like Denmark.
And as you mentioned,
this one is more Japanese.
You know, not many countries
have princesses anymore.
OH! ARE YOU SAYING…
He thought of princesses and wanted you
to experience Denmark and Japan.
-Princess!
-Yes.
-Was it intentional?
-Is that so?
-Is this correct?
-Amazing!
SIGH…
How did he figure out
something I wasn't going to share?
How did you point it out?
It was for the princess experience.
Both Japan and Denmark are countries
that still have princesses.
AND KOREA DOES TOO♥
-That was sharp.
-I got chills.
Princess Sooyoung, please.
That was Chef Hyun-suk's Choipunzel.
Next, Chef Sung-jun's meal,
Into Three New Worlds.
JAMÓN BRUSCHETTA
ANCHOVY OIL PASTA
GONGJU CHESTNUT PANNA COTTA
CHEF KWON SUNG-JUN'S INTO THREE NEW WORLDS
My dishes have a story.
A love story with her.
-Is that so?
-Back there…
-And she has to hear it first?
-Not me.
Yes, she needs to hear it a bit.
I think it'll backfire.
-He'll kill her appetite.
-Exactly.
I think he wants to lose.
Is there a story between you and Sooyoung?
There is.
I waited in front of the fridge
while checking the time
because I was waiting for her
at Yongsan Station, exit three.
First, I give her a flower.
In front of Yongsan Station?
What's he saying?
Can she eat it now?
-That flower.
-Yongsan Station?
So try the appetizer first.
-The appetizer.
-So I got the flower now?
-Yes.
-She got it.
At Yongsan Station.
Why did it have to be Yongsan Station?
Because I live in Yongsan-gu.
He's selfish.
She must've come to Yongsan.
He called her over.
-Is there a ring?
-Is there?
Try the bread, jamón, and the cheese.
That flower looks tough.
-I hope it's not tough.
-Did you want it to be tough?
-Is that like you?
-It's my tenacious love.
LOL
How he loved her through the years.
But food should never be too tough.
-But jamón is always a little tough.
-That's how jamón is.
-What is it?
-Yes?
-Did you find a ring?
What's wrong?
IS THERE A PROBLEM?
HEY
-You had us scared there.
-Really.
There was a heart in the dish.
This is so good.
FEELING PROUD
I really love this pistachio spread.
It's bread, pistachio spread, and jamón.
A mix of three ingredients.
It's the kind of flavor I love.
-He captured her taste.
-All right.
-Is that olive oil on top?
-Just a drizzle.
-Bread, jamón, and pistachio.
-Pistachio.
And a bit of olive oil.
She's frowning a little.
That's the frown you show
when you're moved.
She's starting to clap.
That was the first dish.
The second world among the three worlds.
-It's a date, so we must eat.
-The second.
-You're eating?
-At a pasta place.
It's an anchovy pasta.
Is this seaweed bugak?
I smashed a few
to add the crunchy texture.
-It was intentional.
-I think this was Chef Jong-won's bugak.
-Is that so?
-It is.
I'm curious.
I'm so curious.
-She's curious.
-It should be salty.
-She loves anchovies.
-She makes pasta at home too.
She bought the tinned anchovies
because she liked them.
CHUCKLING
HEY
She's starting to giggle.
-It must be good.
-It must be different from your pasta.
He's so annoying.
Look at his face.
TOTAL ARROGANCE
This salmon isn't too salty.
I didn't add lots of salt to the salmon.
I just added some lemon juice
for some sourness.
-To boost the umami.
-That was why he added water.
And some champagne got in there too.
Yes, it did. There's champagne in there.
-It worked out.
-He popped the bottle.
-Unintentionally?
-He unintentionally helped him.
-I had put some in already.
-You had?
I think he added more for me.
Yes, he added more champagne.
He saw that it could use more sourness,
so he sacrificed himself
and added more into the dish.
Isn't that right?
What?
Will you listen when I talk?
Please stop dozing off!
I was complimenting you.
-You're right.
-Right?
-Yes.
-I see.
He's exhausted.
-The third dish, panna cotta.
-Panna cotta.
I mixed chestnut yanggaeng and milk.
I added oolong tea for aroma
and some vanilla syrup too.
-Oolong tea.
-And topped it with cream cheese.
Did you use the tea I had?
You're right. Oolong tea.
That is such a wonder.
He's not allowed to use
any other oolong tea.
-Yes.
-That's the rule.
Where are you now?
-We're at a café now after dinner.
-Going to a café.
The last stop.
Yongsan must have great joints.
It does. That's true.
PERFECT PUDDING TEXTURE
He did well until now. The last one.
YUM
OH?
ARROGANCE TAKE 2
It must be good.
Why am I drooling so much?
What's it like?
It's probably like melted
and re-hardened chestnut yanggaeng.
But he added oolong tea.
The harmony between the cheese,
this chestnut flavor,
and the overall texture
is nothing but soft and smooth.
I also don't like it
when something tastes overly sweet,
but it must be the oolong tea.
It's so good.
-Koreans love chestnuts.
-We do.
She finished everything. All right.
-Sooyoung.
-Gosh. The Yongsan…
-The Yongsan date.
-Yongsan date.
That was a well-thought-out date.
Now, it's time for you to choose.
This is hard. It must be.
Press one for Sung-jun
and two for Hyun-suk.
Make your decision
and please press the button.
Did you press it?
Oh, no.
She did.
She came to a decision
and made her choice.
-It's breaking my heart.
-It's breaking her heart.
-And because of who?
-Breaking her heart?
Which meal did she choose?
Let's find out the result. Show us.
Rule of the Princess's Dish.
Is it Sung-jun, who kept Sooyoung
as his bias since the day she debuted?
Or is it Hyun-suk, who claims
Sooyoung must stand in the middle?
Who's going to be the winner?
Can Sung-jun get a second date?
Who did Sooyoung choose?
-I'm nervous.
-Who did she choose?
KWON SUNG-JUN WINS
INTO THREE NEW WORLDS WINS
It was Sung-jun.
Sung-jun wins.
SOOYOUNG'S HUBBY WINS
Into Three New Worlds.
Sung-jun's wish came true.
And he broke the jinx.
He had lost all ten cook-offs
involving K-pop stars,
-It's my first win.
-…but he finally broke his jinx.
Sooyoung chose you,
which puts you in a tie
with Hyun-suk at eight stars.
-Eight stars.
-Eight?
You have abandoned Chef Hyun-suk
and chosen Chef Sung-jun, so why?
"Abandoned"?
It all came down to this dessert.
-This was so…
-All dates need a dessert.
It's so crazy
because I got this chestnut yanggaeng
a few days ago at a meeting
for a film festival screening.
There was a whole set.
Some chose the plain red bean ones
while others took the ones with chestnuts,
-so I also had taken one of them.
-It was that.
It's so crazy that he made this with that.
-That's Chef & My Fridge.
-Exactly.
This was such a witty dish.
He definitely has great taste.
-I do.
-I see.
But Chef Hyun-suk's pasta
was really delicious too.
And for that appetizer
with the yuja pepper paste,
-I'll definitely try to make it myself.
-I see.
You suffered a loss on your birthday.
Right, it's his birthday.
He can't smile
even though it's his birthday.
The toughest thing for me today
isn't my loss.
It's that I must watch him dance again.
That's true.
-He'll have to dance.
-He'll get his wish again.
"Into the New World."
-Please put a star on him.
-Do I do it? Okay.
Please give him a star.
This is Sung-jun's eighth win!
His wish came true.
-He gets a star from Sooyoung.
-Thank you.
-It was so delicious.
-After waiting 20 years.
HIS WISH CAME TRUE
Congratulations.
Now for the second cook-off
played with Sooyoung's ingredients.
He can't be bothered with anything
except for food, Chef Yoon Nam-no.
She can't be bothered with anything
except for dancing, Chef Park Eun-yeong.
I guess Nam-no couldn't be bothered
to win stars this year.
You have two now, right?
It's a secret.
He has two.
You won in the last episode,
so you have two.
-Yes.
-At least you won.
I heard you were thrilled.
That day,
I had gopchang-jeongol by myself.
-Really? Alone?
-How adorable.
-You can eat it alone.
-He's so adorable.
-He eats when he loses and when he wins.
-And when he wins.
He has many reasons to eat.
Eun-yeong is in a pinch right now.
-Right?
-She picked the wrong guy.
-She lost four times in a row.
-Four times.
-She has been down lately.
-Four?
But you also said
this was a perfect order for you.
I can also be very lazy sometimes,
so we have something in common.
When I lived alone in Hong Kong,
no one was there to do my laundry.
So it had been piling up and up,
and in the end,
I had nothing to wear.
So I finally decided to do the laundry,
lifted the pile of clothes,
and they had gone moldy.
It was that bad?
That's how far I'll go.
Excuse me.
That's not laziness. It's gross.
Why share such a story?
When I lived in Hong Kong,
I literally had
mushrooms growing in my bathroom.
-Wait.
-Eun-yeong.
Pull yourself together, Eun-yeong.
SUSPICIONS OF ADDING MSG TO THE STORY
Mushrooms grew there?
-I'm not that bad.
-You aren't, right?
I'm not that bad.
The fridge owner feels uncomfortable.
I'm saying that
my laziness is that extreme.
APPROVED
-It's your laziness.
-That's true.
Nam-no, you ended up at a hospital once
because you couldn't be bothered?
-What?
-What is it?
One day, I was craving ramyeon.
So I microwaved it.
I had thrown in two eggs inside too.
NO, WAIT…
-And that egg blew up in my mouth.
-It would.
So I had to pay 100,000 won
because my mouth got skinned.
-From a burn?
-I got burnt.
The egg stayed swollen
when it came out of the microwave.
It hadn't blown up yet,
but it must've blown up
the moment he bit into it.
If he spent time after pulling it out,
getting kimchi, and sitting down,
it would've been fine.
This means he ate it
as soon as he took it out.
He put it in his mouth right away.
Yes, I ate it right away,
and it blew up with a bang.
The bowl was still in the microwave.
-He put his head inside it.
-He ate it right away.
SUCH A FRIGHTENING STORY
These stories aren't helping them.
BUT CAN THEIR DISHES HELP THEM?
CHEF NAM-NO'S INGREDIENTS:
AVOCADO, MINI CUCUMBER, CHERRY TOMATO
LEMON, ARUGULA, BURRATA, SEAWEED BUGAK,
CHILI OIL, OYSTER SAUCE, AND MORE
What are you making, Chef Nam-no?
I prepared a dish called
Right Now, It's Nam-no's Generation!
From now on, it's Nam-no's Generation.
Forever Nam-no's Generation!
All right.
GIRLS' GENERATION IS PLEASED
-Right Now, It's Nam-no's Generation!
-That was great.
-So your time is here?
-It is.
I will not use a knife today.
SURPRISED
I will not use a cutting board,
and I will not use scissors either.
-That's awesome.
-How will you cut things?
With your teeth? Is that it?
-No knives, and no scissors?
-No.
I prepared two dishes.
-Two?
First, canapes made with an avocado.
Canape. He'll mash it.
Next, I'll make
an easy version of dandan noodles.
-Dandan noodles?
-That sounds so good.
Then you'll have to chop the ingredients.
-Will he chop them?
-Are you using a blender?
-I will not use a blender.
-What?
Wait.
Wait a second.
You shouldn't complicate it further
by not using any tools.
-She has a point.
-Yes.
He had the wrong idea.
I haven't thought of that.
Then you won't have too many dirty dishes.
No, not too many dirty dishes.
And less labor.
It'd be great
if he can make something delicious
with minimum effort,
and while using fewer dishes.
The one thing he's using the least now
is his brain.
Come on.
-I will not use my brain.
-You're too harsh.
CHEF EUN-YEONG'S INGREDIENTS:
BRISKET, SOFT TOFU, TTEOKGUK RICE CAKE
CHILI OIL, OYSTER SAUCE, CHICKEN STOCK,
BLUEBERRY, PEACH, HONEY, AND MORE
Up against him is Chef Eun-yeong.
What's your dish?
My dish is called…
MicrowaGee, Gee, Gee, Gee, Gee
Microwa…
WIPING
CHEF PARK EUN-YEONG'S MICROWAGEE
That's awesome.
Her eyes were normal
while dancing for the first time.
EYES ARE STILL ALIVE
I've been enjoying dancing,
so I fixed my eyes.
But that makes you lose your charm.
-MicrowaGee, gee, gee, gee
-Baby, baby
I'm using only the microwave to cook.
Nothing on the stove.
That's awesome.
I also won't use
a knife or a cutting board.
I'm going to make mapo tofu.
Mapo tofu?
It has to boil hard over heat
to be the most delicious,
but I'll use the microwave
and even add a smoky flavor.
You can do that with a microwave?
-I should learn from her.
-So first, mapo tofu.
And since it's summer,
I'll make blueberry bingsu.
-I'll throw that in too.
-Bingsu?
So Nam-no,
even today, you won't win a star.
Gee, gee, gee, gee
Nam-no, even today, you won't win a star.
Let us begin this cook-off for Sooyoung,
Don't Skip Meals Because
-You Can't Be Bothered.
-This is crazy.
You can do this!
I'm excited to see
this new genre of dishes.
This woman can take Nam-no down easily,
without even using the stove,
Chef Park Eun-yeong.
This guy will chop Eun-yeong into pieces
without any knives or scissors,
Chef Yoon Nam-no.
Which chef will the lazy Sooyoung choose?
Let the 15-minute cook-off begin!
Begin!
A DISH FOR THE LAZY PERSON
NAM-NO CUTS AN AVOCADO
Is that a knife?
It's a spatula.
Wait.
-Come on.
Just use scissors instead.
-Boo.
-Why?
She's really using scissors.
She's not using a knife. Only scissors.
That's literally how I cut green onions.
-She's doing that.
-Yes.
WHAT ABOUT NAM-NO AND THE SPATULA?
CHOPPING OFF MINI CUCUMBER TIPS
CHUCKLING IN DISBELIEF
Look what he's doing.
It's a strongman's show.
AVOCADO
-Huh?
-Huh? It's spoiled.
THE AVOCADO IS SPOILED
-The avocado went bad.
-Is it spoiled?
-Has it gone bad?
-Yes.
Emergency.
-That's not good.
-It's one of his key ingredients.
-What about that one?
-What a relief.
One of them was fine.
RELIEVED
Thank god that one was fine.
1. PREP AN AVOCADO
-It would've been all over.
-It would've been bad.
SNIP
STILL CUTTING THE GREEN ONION…
-Wait, Chef Eun-yeong.
-Chef Eun-yeong.
Just use a knife.
-Using a knife would've been faster.
-It would've been faster.
-No.
-She's just…
You can use a knife.
She's telling you to use it.
They'll start to hurt her grip very soon.
-Using a knife…
-How tough.
-…also means using a board.
-It's not like Sooyoung said
you aren't allowed to use a knife.
-I never said that.
-Exactly.
BANGING
He's using a stick.
CRUSHING MINI CUCUMBERS WITH A STICK
He's using lots of tools.
Do you have that stick at home, Sooyoung?
-No, I don't.
-Jeez.
-Should've used your fist.
-Use your fist.
You're using your fist?
He's smashing them with his fist.
2. SMASH MINI CUCUMBERS WITH YOUR FIST(?)
Sooyoung doesn't have that stick at home.
That'll hurt your hands more!
Just use the back of a knife.
What's he doing now?
Giving a Thai massage?
Guys.
Just use a board and a knife.
-To cut down on dirty dishes.
-I feel anxious without a cutting board.
They're doing it all in a pan.
Instead of using tools,
they're trying to get things done
using their own bodies.
Yes. It's been two minutes.
It looks like there's more labor involved.
JIFFY NAM-NO
What do you want?
-Chili oil.
-Chili oil?
Vinegar?
Vinegar.
3. MIX CUCUMBER WITH CONDIMENTS
CUCUMBER SALAD SEASONING, FINISHED
ALSO DONE WITH MAPO TOFU SEASONING
INTO THE MICROWAGEE
It's going in.
GRABS THE SCISSORS AGAIN
Eun-yeong, just use a knife.
-Just use a knife already.
-No.
-Just use a knife.
-Just use it.
People who can't be bothered
-never use a knife.
-It's uncomfortable to watch!
-It's uncomfortable to watch.
-It is.
It's making us feel uncomfortable.
CHERRY TOMATOES IN A BAG
-Tomatoes?
-Tomatoes.
Will he beat those too?
You might pop the bag,
so you'd better be careful.
He's pressing it down
with his body weight.
Can Sooyoung also put in that much power?
To press with that much power,
she needs to jump off the first floor.
1ST FLOOR, LIKE JUMPING IN PLACE?
He added white balsamic vinegar.
NEXT, BOIL NOODLES!
-Is he cooking ramyeon?
-He is.
TWO PORTIONS OF THE NOODLES
How many are you making?
Don't cook for yourself again.
We told you
not to cook for yourself again.
-Wait, how many? Four?
-Four?
Think before you act!
Hey, think before you add those.
The more noodles, the more delicious.
Don't make it the way you usually do.
He can eat four bags of it?
WHY DOES EUN-YEONG
SEEM SO RELAXED IN COMPARISON?
She's chill.
You must need lots of starch.
Why do you need that?
I have to add it to mapo tofu
to make it thicker.
-It's for the thickness.
-The thickness.
She usually has to throw that in
while the soup boils hard,
so it'll be difficult for her
to take it out, pour, and put it back in.
GRANDPA, I'LL SHOW YOU!
-Is that the mapo tofu sauce?
-Yes, it's the sauce.
OYSTER SAUCE, CHICKEN STOCK, SOY SAUCE
That's a nice color.
Isn't it too thin for a mapo tofu sauce?
-She'll add starch.
-Oh, she'll use starch?
Starch will cook right away
when it goes into hot water.
Just mix it well.
-It'll gelatinize when it's warm enough.
-Really?
-About 75°C should be enough.
-Is that okay?
STARCH GELATINIZATION WORKS WELL AT 75°C
He's actually making ramyeon.
He's adding the flakes.
He's just making ramyeon.
Are you making ramyeon?
I am. She has no other noodles.
SETS THE TIMER FOR THE NOODLES
Oyster sauce.
-Dandan noodles?
-Oyster sauce.
Chicken stock.
ONE RAMYEON SOUP BASE
Hey, it's a peanut sauce.
He added peanut butter.
SOY SAUCE, SUGAR, SESAME OIL
DANDAN NOODLE SAUCE IS READY
Eight minutes.
Seriously?
You now have eight minutes.
STILL WORKING ON THE STARCH GELATINIZATION
THE SAUCE BECAME THICKER
That seems like a bigger hassle.
It's not.
You would've been done if you used a pan.
To prevent her from skipping meals
because she can't be bothered,
-the recipe needs to be simple.
-Right.
They're just not using tools.
They're both putting in too much work.
You won't see
any dirty dishes on this side.
Right. You have a point.
She'll just eat it and that'll be it.
-Also, add some tteok, rice cake.
-Rice cake?
That'll make the sauce too thick.
It'll become too thick.
She'll add tofu.
-It adds water.
-Just like that.
It looks like mapo tofu.
-Are you going to microwave it again?
-I will.
It'd be better to use a pan.
Yes, it would've been better.
BACK INTO THE MICROWAVE
BEEP
THE NOODLES ARE DONE
Four portions of ramyeon noodles
are ready.
-Four servings.
-Four.
Why did he make so much?
He's getting paid right now.
-Will he just use the noodles?
-He'll mix them with the sauce,
dandan noodle sauce.
That's a hefty amount just for tasting.
5. COOL COOKED RAMYEON IN COLD WATER
-Just the noodles?
-He'll mix them with the sauce.
It's hot.
IMMERSION BLENDER
Wait a second!
-Why did she pull that out?
-What?
She picked up an immersion blender.
FROZEN BLUEBERRIES
-For the bingsu.
-Bingsu.
-Listen.
Either eat this one
or the microwaved dish.
You'll use only one cooking tool.
FROZEN BLUEBERRIES
They're frozen.
You kept them frozen.
It's to make bingsu.
-That freezer works well.
-It does.
EPISODE 78, THE BINGSU IN THE FREEZER
It melted more in the freezer.
IT TURNED INTO BINGO MANGSU…
-That freezer works well.
-It does.
Last time, we ended up
with hwachae, fruit punch.
BEGINS TO MAKE BINGSU
What did you just add?
-Cream cheese?
-I added cream cheese.
This is honey.
Honey and milk.
That has to be good.
It'll turn out like ice cream.
-Really?
-It's frozen now.
That looks so good.
4. BLEND BLUEBERRIES,
CREAM CHEESE, HONEY, AND MILK
She's adding an egg.
Will you blow it up?
-What?
-An egg in mapo tofu?
Will she blow it up to make it smoky?
It's going in.
I have a bad feeling.
I think the egg will blow up.
I learned today that
microwaving an egg will make it blow up.
-Really? It blows up.
-It does.
The yolk blows up.
NAM-NO IS STILL COOLING THE NOODLES
It would've cooled down by now
if you made just one serving.
-But he made four.
-This is crazy.
Five minutes left.
Please check the dishes, Jung-hwan.
-You have to hurry.
-Oh, gosh.
OH, NO…
It's not so easy to cook
without a knife, a cutting board,
or even the stove.
But they're somehow managing.
Will that turn into bingsu?
Mmm. It's so good.
Is it really?
It doesn't look like bingsu to me.
It'll probably taste like a smoothie.
-Shouldn't you put it in the freezer?
-It's going in.
INTO THE FREEZER FOR A MOMENT
Should I try the blueberry bingsu?
Yes.
Blueberry smoothie.
A cold treat for the summer,
blueberry bingsu.
Is it good enough
to end her four-loss streak?
SO?
…four-loss streak?
It is.
Will she finally win?
-It's perfect for this weather.
-Really?
-It's amazing.
What's this smell?
It has more flavor
because I added cream cheese.
It tastes luxurious,
thanks to the cream cheese.
That's a great tip.
LET'S GO, YOON NAM-NO!
6. MIX AVOCADO, AVOCADO OIL,
OLIVE OIL, SALT, AND WASABI
TO MAKE AVOCADO MOUSSE
-Nam-no starts plating his food.
-Yoon Nam-no.
A FINAL TOUCH WITH LEMON ZEST
Can you put this out?
-Nam-no is done with something.
-Canapes.
All he needs to serve now
are the dandan noodles.
MEANWHILE, PARK EUN-YEONG…
SHE'S CUTTING A PEACH WITH SCISSORS…
-Just use a knife.
-Please.
People who can't be bothered
don't want to use too many tools.
Just use a knife! Please!
You're making us uncomfortable.
I feel like it's all my fault
for saying I'm lazy.
I'll have to use a cutting board,
which lazy people don't.
Watch your hands.
Chefs need to take care of their hands.
DROPPING THE DANDAN NOODLE SAUCE
INTO THE NOODLES
Nam-no is working with ramyeon…
What did you add to this?
I made a peanut butter sauce.
Peanut butter sauce?
LOTS OF NOODLES
7. TOP WITH BURRATA AND ARUGULA
It almost looks like a pasta.
Is that arugula?
Try it and see if it's seasoned well.
Let me do that.
Is it seasoned well?
He made a lot of noodles.
-He's trying the noodles.
-He'll add something.
-Jung-hwan.
-Yes?
Here I go.
Now, so?
Will Nam-no's generation finally come?
It's right now.
RIGHT NOW, IT'S NAM-NO'S GENERATION!
-It's Nam-no's generation.
-It is?
The peanut taste goes so well with this.
8. TOP NOODLES WITH CHILI OIL
AND CRUSHED SEAWEED BUGAK
But it's not spicy.
-It's mostly sweet and nutty.
-He'll add chili oil.
He just added chili oil.
So he just added it.
I tried only the noodles.
This is amazing.
DAZED…
-Why are you standing around, Eun-yeong?
-Right now?
The microwave should be done.
People who can't be bothered
don't work tirelessly like him.
-They dance and take it slow.
-She's dancing.
She's addicted to dancing.
-What are you up to?
-Go away.
-Please!
-Why?
-What's up?
-Just go away.
-Go to your spot.
-She's bothering him.
Only Nam-no's working like crazy.
Can you take this?
It's time to wrap up. 50 seconds.
ONLY CUCUMBER SALAD REMAINS
SESAME
BALSAMIC TOMATOES
Thirty seconds.
-He's done.
-Nam-no is done.
RIGHT NOW, IT'S NAM-NO'S GENERATION
IS DONE FIRST
Nam-no is done.
-Hurry.
-Twenty seconds.
Eun-yeong has enough time.
Hurry up. Time's almost up.
Hurry up. 20 seconds.
-Ten seconds.
-It's almost time now. Ten.
-Nine. Eight.
-Eight.
-Seven. Six. Five.
-The microwave.
-Hurry.
-Four. Three.
-Three.
-Two. One.
-Time's up.
-You have to finish up, Eun-yeong.
Okay. Chef Eun-yeong is done.
MICROWAGEE IS FINISHED TOO
It smells like sundubu-jjigae,
soft tofu stew.
It's somewhere between
sundubu-jjigae and mapo tofu.
I love that.
The egg hasn't been cooked.
-Did she cover it up with sesame?
-She did.
She covered it up.
That's a smart move.
What did she hide?
Once you mix it, it'll cook.
It was intentional.
NAM-NO EATS THE LEFTOVER NOODLES
SO GOOD
And now, both dishes
are ready for Sooyoung.
AMAZED
It's amazing that they did this
without using too many tools.
I'm so excited right now.
My mouth is already watering.
Nam-no made three dishes
and finished first.
-He did.
-Yes.
-Oh, I made three.
-Will his generation begin?
ALREADY FORGOT
1. DANDAN NOODLES
2. AVOCADO CANAPE
3. CUCUMBER SALAD
CHEF YOON NAM-NO'S
RIGHT NOW, IT'S NAM-NO'S GENERATION!
First try the canape, then the noodles.
-Canape.
-Then have the cucumber salad
-like a side dish when you need it.
-When she needs it?
Yes, that's the appetizer.
A BIG BITE
He made that with an avocado.
-Is that seaweed bugak at the bottom?
-Yes.
That alone should be flavorful already.
-Jong-won's bugak.
-You don't seem happy.
IS IT BAD?
It's not that.
I frown when something tastes good.
AH-HA
She frowns when something is good.
Did you add wasabi?
Yes, to add a bit of spice,
and some avocado oil.
I see. Avocado oil.
It feels like a bar snack.
It can be a bar snack,
or brunch, whatever you want it to be.
-Right.
-I just mashed some stuff together.
It doesn't suit mornings.
-He called it a canape.
-I should've thought it through.
It's really good.
Bugak is already seasoned.
Chef Jong-won's bugak
is playing a big role today.
-They're making use of it.
-It's good.
What was your intention behind this bugak?
"Bugak" is important in itself,
but I wanted to "bring out"
other ingredients.
A COMEDIAN
Bugak "brings out" other ingredients.
Sung-jun issues a warning.
Dandan noodles.
There's chili oil down there.
-Is this burrata?
-Burrata.
It is, but I only used the creamy center.
I wanted you to enjoy the smooth texture.
-Sounds good.
-It looks soft.
I feel like I just became rich.
-Whoa.
-Those are just regular ramyeon noodles.
-Yes, regular ramyeon.
-Yes.
I still don't get
why he made four servings.
Did you serve all of it?
I left mine on the side.
-Over there?
-This is just one serving.
He had about a bag while tasting it.
SNIFF
What is it?
Does it smell good?
-It smells…
-It smells how?
…so delicious.
Does it smell like dandan noodles?
TRUSTS HIM AND TAKES A BIG BITE
-It's made with peanuts, so probably.
-It looks good.
She's frowning again because it's so good.
DEPRESSED, PROUD
What's it like?
THINKING…
But you can't eat more than a bite.
A SUDDEN ATTACK(?)
-Did it taste too intense?
-It's intense.
You feel happy with the first bite,
but it's a huge amount of happiness.
-Wait, no.
-What is it?
The spiciness just kicked in.
I can go back for more.
You need that spiciness.
-It was the chili oil.
-Chili oil.
It hit me toward the end.
A DASH OF FLAVOR VARIATION
-It's a fancy dish.
-One more bite.
-Try the cucumber salad too.
-A refreshing bite.
-And enjoy the sourness.
-So you keep eating it.
I thought it'd be too dry
since it didn't look too saucy.
It's really delicious.
The last dish.
This is like a palate cleanser?
Gosh.
Cucumbers smell so good.
The moment I smelled it,
it reminded me of cold cucumber soup.
-Is it like that?
-Yes.
The mix must be perfect.
Cold cucumber soup is great in summer.
You're so witty.
THE PRINCESS SHOOTS OUT HEARTS
HOLDING HIM IN CHECK?
It refreshes my mouth in an instant.
FRESH FLAVORS OF CUCUMBERS AND TOMATOES
I'm sure there's a reason why he made it.
EXCITED NAM-NO
You pressed down on the cucumbers
and tomatoes back there, right?
How does that help?
I wanted to release its juice
and salt it to let it draw out the water.
So it can get seasoned
in a short period of time.
To salt it in a short period of time.
I guess that's how he did it so quickly.
-It's so good.
-I see.
There are other dishes,
so why don't we stop for now?
Next, Chef Eun-yeong's dish…
MicrowaGee, Gee, Gee, Gee
MAPO TOFU MADE WITH A MICROWAVE
BLUEBERRY BINGSU
(MADE WITH AN IMMERSION BLENDER)
CHEF PARK EUN-YEONG'S MICROWAGEE
That egg holds the key.
It's still hot at the bottom,
so you can cook the egg in the heat.
It's cooked.
It's slightly cooked.
-Some time has passed.
-While she waited?
-It's perfect.
-It looks perfect?
THE CHINESE SISTER FEELS PROUD
She calculated everything.
I wonder what it's like.
-Will it taste like mapo tofu?
-Right?
YUM
SO HOT
OVERLY IMMERSED
OH, GOSH
-You were inconsiderate.
-Oh, no.
What have you done to my Sooyoung?
So inconsiderate.
THIS IS WHAT I WANTED, GEE
So it's both hot and delicious?
-Is it spicy?
-Just enough to be delicious.
-Yes.
I've been having trouble
trying to get rid of the rice cake,
and I had no idea
you'd put it into mapo tofu.
Many people eat it with rice,
but I didn't think
you would've had it with rice cakes.
I wanted to serve you a nice dish
with a mix of carbs and protein,
a perfect meal, so to speak.
So you used rice cakes
instead of serving rice?
You ended up giving
her unhinged rice cakes a makeover.
-It looks hot.
-She's fighting heat with heat.
If it's that hot,
why can't you just blow on it?
-There's a reason.
-You might burn your mouth.
-Tofu has a fluffy texture,
-Yes.
-…and so do eggs.
-True.
Also, the sauce is hot right now,
-and I like to enjoy it while it's hot.
-So you like your food hot?
Also, rice cakes can contain heat inside.
Yes, if you eat rice cakes the wrong way,
you might even lose a tooth.
-A tooth?
-You can lose a tooth.
It really happens.
GOOD GRIEF
There's always someone like that
in a country village.
WHAT KIND OF COUNTRYSIDE
IS HE TALKING ABOUT?
CONTINUES TO EAT
DESPITE THE RISK OF LOSING HER TEETH(?)
-This is going to be hard.
-She keeps eating it.
I thought she'd stop
because it was too hot.
While I'm eating this scorching hot dish,
I can still see this.
-Blueberry bingsu.
-It must be exciting.
It's exciting and nice to see it there.
-Your mouth must feel hot.
-The temperature difference.
Next, blueberry bingsu.
It'll refresh your mouth.
And cool it down.
Will that be the decisive factor?
-She just likes desserts.
-She likes desserts.
Sooyoung always needs a dessert.
Nice try, Nam-no.
I want to see this thing for sale.
Is it that good?
It's simple, so make it at home.
Just blend everything together.
INHALES
I can't be bothered to wash the blender.
UNDERSTANDABLE
Because of the cream cheese,
I find myself thinking,
"Is it less refreshing?"
But then a piece of peach gets right in.
It's very refreshing and delicious.
And because of that,
this is a great dish to eat
-along with this. The balance is great.
-The balance must be great.
BOTH MEALS RECEIVE GREAT COMPLIMENTS
It's so tough to choose.
Now, let's try Chef Nam-no's dish first.
MMM
It's mild and delicious. And nutty.
Mild, delicious, and nutty.
Just eating this will fill me up.
Really?
Why do you have so much left?
WANT SOME?
It wouldn't have been
as good without the chili oil.
OR EAT IT WITH REFRESHING CUCUMBER SALAD
DECIDED TO JOIN HIM
It's good.
RESPONDS IMMEDIATELY
This is good.
I really want to know the recipe.
It has a bang at the end.
-It's so good.
-Really?
The sauce ratio is very easy.
My kids would love this.
I have to take the recipe from Nam-no.
Is that hard to make?
No, it's just one each.
-Peanut butter. Soy sauce.
-Soy sauce.
-Oyster sauce, sugar.
And sesame oil.
It's so good.
It's a nice dish to make for the summer.
It's like cold ramyeon.
He mixed the tomatoes
with cucumber, including the juice,
and that brought out the umami.
It's so good.
It's good.
-Thank you.
-"It's good."
Next, Chef Eun-yeong's dish.
MicrowaGee.
It's not like mapo tofu,
but more like tteokbokki.
EYES OPENED WIDE
-It tastes pleasantly spicy.
-It does.
-It's so good.
-Like Chinese-style brisket tteokbokki.
-It's sweet.
But when the tofu melts,
it also feels like a healthy dish.
I want to eat something like this
while watching mukbang at night.
NODDING
It would be easy on your stomach
even if you eat it late at night.
-It's such a mild mapo tofu.
-It wouldn't even make you fat.
It would be great
if this could be sold as a meal kit,
-something you can microwave and eat.
-Yes.
You can only call the dish mapo tofu
if you use doubanjiang.
People usually don't have that,
but they'll have gochujang.
So try making it with gochujang as I did.
-I think that suits our palate better.
-Right.
-Please try the dessert.
-Okay.
MMM♥
-It's a perfect way to wrap up the meal.
-It is.
A perfect ending.
It's a nice and mild finish.
-It doesn't make you feel guilty either.
-Desserts are important.
What now? You're in trouble.
FEELS GUILTY(?) OVER HER CHOICE
It's a really difficult decision.
You have lots.
-Make a decision.
-It's been a while.
Press one for Eun-yeong,
or press two for Nam-no.
Make your decision
and press the button!
It'll be a fatal blow
to whoever doesn't get a star.
They both did so well.
-They did a great job.
-I'm sorry.
-Did you press it?
-Yes.
-You did?
SHE CHOSE JUST ONE PERSON
AFTER A LOT OF THOUGHT
Let's find out
who Sooyoung chose. Show us.
Don't Skip Meals
Because You Can't Be Bothered
If Eun-yeong wins,
she'll break her four-loss streak.
If Nam-no wins,
he'll begin his winning streak.
Who did Sooyoung choose?
A dish she can make
even when she can't be bothered.
Which one made that?
Who's the winner?
PARK EUN-YEONG WINS
It's Park Eun-yeong.
CHEF PARK EUN-YEONG'S MICROWAGEE WINS
Eun-yeong wins the round.
-She wins this round.
-She just loves desserts.
She finally breaks her losing streak.
I'm the type who enjoys the flavors
from typical Korean cuisine.
When she said it was mapo tofu,
I thought it'd taste like a Chinese dish.
-But it tasted a bit like tteokbokki.
-Yes.
Also, it was a dish I would
actually get around to making at home.
I'm going to try it.
-Adding gochujang was the winning move.
-It was.
It tasted like
something my mom would make.
-It did.
-Like the mapo tofu our moms would make.
Also, adding rice cakes
instead of rice was a big win.
Is Nam-no's generation yet to come?
-Is it not your generation yet?
-Right?
I've eaten a hearty amount today,
so I'm fine.
HOW ADORABLE
Please put a star on Chef Eun-yeong.
-Great job.
This is her sixth win,
and she's back on track.
Congratulations.
Congratulations, Eun-yeong.
NAM-NO'S GENERATION SHALL COME
Her career has been going strong
ever since her debut.
Do you feel the generational gap?
Not really.
Chef & My Fridge, yaho!
KNOWS ALL THE MEMES
The young guns of the show
just shoot right home.
She said, "Let's go to a karaoke room!"
You had fun that day, right?
It was so much fun, Jung-hwa!
SOCIAL MODE ON
We present Jung-hwa's fridge!
I love carrots so much.
That's a zucchini.
It's delicious when grilled.
Let the 15-minute cook-off
for Jung-hwa begin!
A NEW WORLD OF VEGETABLE DISHES
Yareu!
He seems way more confident.
I'm going to chop everything.
HIS MOUTH IS STILL ADJUSTING
It's really good!
Yareu!
IF IT'S GOOD, SAY "YAHO!"
THE FIRST 2 VS. 2 TAG TEAM ROUND
THE MOST EXTREME TEAMWORK MATCH
Salt.
SMALL VOICE, PERFECT TEAMWORK
THE CHEF AND THE KITCHEN TOOLMAN
UH! UGH!
BUT THEIR OPPONENTS ARE…
That's what I'm talking about!
…THE LOUD AND CRAZY CHINESE SIBLINGS
You're cheating.
They're flustered.
WHAT A TOTAL MESS
WHAT WILL HAPPEN IN THE TAG TEAM ROUND?
Can you call this a team round?
-Yareu.
-Today is the death of yareu as a meme.
-The death.
Subtitle translation by: Eunsook Youn